The Orca Full Cat Silly Queen!
Yay!
Come on. Come on.
Ah!
Oh, that's good!
Spix!
Correct!
Sport!
Oh!
That's great!
Here we go!
Come on, we're stuck with Mr. Bank!
Let's continue. This is an opportunity problem. Please say it early.
Say the seventh step of 99.
Go, go, go!
Let's go. Please say the seventh step. All of them.
Seven, nine, eight, seven, nine, two, three, two, one, seven, two, one, seven, five, three, two, five, one, six, four, ten, two, seven, seven, four, ten, two, one, seven, eight, five, six, seven, nine, six, ten, three
Someone said it was hard to hear, didn't they?
He said it, just now.
Seven-seven what?
One, two, eight.
Yes, that's OK.
Let's go. Please demonstrate the gag that once dominated the world, "Kato Chanpe! which once dominated the world.
Ah, He-chan?
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha. It's the best, isn't it?
Then, please say it to the camera.
Kato-chanpe.
Correct! Excellent.
Oh!
Cute. Cute.
Cute.
Did you know her from Kanbo?
Yes!
Can I ask you to do it one more time?
I'm a little shy.
I can't make it big, like this.
Like this.
Let's move on to the next question. What is the 4-letter word for a very low price?
Fill in the blanks. Honyara-san, it's "Honyara. Here it is.
What is the one that goes between these two? It means that the price is very cheap.
Chie, did you get it? Now, you look like a fool walking. Let's go.
Twenty-three?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Just a little bit.
Okay, I remember, I remember.
Two is two, two.
I made one mistake, but I have no right.
Oh, really?
I gave you a hint.
Okay, Mr. Matsumoto, let's go.
Please take it.
Two or three mon.
What is it?
Yes, one break.
Okay, let's go.
Here it comes! Eh, eh, eh, here it comes!
That's amazing.
We would all be embarrassed if we could answer this.
Twenty-three percent of them.
No, it's not.
I was stupid to get my hopes up.
What is it?
The old money is coming in.
Ha!
It's here! Mr. Nonaka is here! 2 yuan 3 yen.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Why did you put Chinese money in!
The exchange rate is going crazy. Well, I'll put one in for you.
Yes, please. Two pairs!
No, hey, you have no right! You have no right!
If you make a mistake once, your right is to return the next 1,000 yen!
You idiot!
Is that what this is about?
I want to trust you! I want to!
I want it fast!
I wanna do it now!
Do you understand? You have no right, so!
Oh, I get it!
Tako-chan, like I said before, you have to listen to me about longevity.
No, I don't.
No, no, no, not that way?
Wait a minute. Takane, what's wrong?
Because I know! I know! I know! I know! I know!
Because you're not a... No, that's why I don't have a sword!
I know, I know! Sure! Sure! Okay, okay! Sure! Sure!
Why don't you understand the rules! Like this! Like this!
What is this? Like this!
What is it? Is it a natural gymnastics exercise? Like this!
Finished!
Well, Manaba-san, let's go. Manaba-san, is that correct?
What? A water plant!
Correct!
It's just, it's not a slip. It's not a mistake. I knew it!
It's not a mistake.
What's the distance?
Here's a chance question. Who is the person written on the current 1,000-yen bill?
Ah, here he comes! What is the correct answer? Correct answer!
It was a chance question, wasn't it? Let's go on and on. This is a writing problem.
Draw a diagram of a cone.
It came out slowly. Which way? Which is it? Let's write it down, everyone. It is a cone.
You all shouldn't react as if you've never heard of it before.
Well, well, well. Well, that's all right. Correct.
I'd like a little more. That's right. That's right.
Not too cheap.
Well, there's no extra charge.
It's gone. It's just gone.
I'm not making the development.
It's okay. Just this circle will do.
Yes, but it's the right answer.
Now the idiots are getting closer.
Let's answer the question.
Kenji Miyazawa published a collection of short stories before his death.
"The Restaurant of Many Dishes"?
Huh! Haa!
Yes, let's go, Mr. Ske!
Correct.
That's good. You look very smart when you can answer this kind of literature and so on.
That's great. Have you read it?
Yes, I have. In a textbook.
Oh, right. You mean you didn't understand what was in the textbook?
That's what compulsory education is all about, isn't it?
Here's your chance problem. Let's go.
What are the principles of viewpoint, point of force, and point of action?
Yes!
Here it is!
Fleming's law.
No, it's not.
What? Isn't it?
What?
There's more.
Can I go one more time?
What? No.
Come on, Ms. Imai.
The techno principle.
Correct!
Good!
That's good.
Here we go, and here we go, and here we go, and here we go.
Please answer all four prefectures in Shikoku.
Here they come... the four prefectures of Shikoku.
Kagawa, Tokushima, Ehime.Kagawa Tokushima Construction Ehime
Correct
Wonderful that!
Reach Reach Reach
Reach Reach
Reach, reach, reach.
It's not leech leech.
We're the fastest in terms of numbers.
Is that so?
Well, good luck to the rest of the group.
There are two of them.
Here's a picture.
This one's pretty good, too. It's easy.
What is this building in Spain?
Well, I wonder what it is.
Well, here it is!
Sacrado Familia.
Correct!
Cool!
Takaneko Bi Movie Show!
Are you okay? Matsui-san, are you okay?
Did you understand? Did you know?
I've never seen it before.
And now, on to the next question.
This is another chance question.
I think you should say this one.
Who is the current Prime Minister of Japan?
The first prime minister.
SeniorSeniors.
Some of you have never heard of Prime Minister before.
I don't know the word "prime minister.
Is prime minister a chief of staff?
What's a prime minister?
Prime Minister.
Prime Minister? Did you answer?
I don't know which one it is either.
It's amazing, isn't it? We're not making any progress.
The conversation has stalled.
Mr. Prime Minister.
Prime Minister.
I'm afraid I've gone too far.
Don't scare me. This is the time of year.
No, don't scare him.
Prime Minister.
Thank you for watching.